filmyfolks.com 2016-03-05

# Privacy Policy of filmyfolks.com.

### Privacy Policy

filmyfolks.com will respect the privacy policy of the viewers of our site. Your use of the filmyfolks Site will not save any personal information that subjects you. fimlyfolks.com is in reach to all viewers and is free of cost. Our site will guide you with the hyperlinks to browse on. Filmyfolks.com takes your privacy very seriously. 

### Information we gather

We collect information from various sources and provide the utmost true information best of us. We also have possibility to gather information from our own members. Our goal is to provide prime information and maintain long-lasting relation with the website visitors.   
As you browse our Web site, servers collect information about your visit, not about you personally. Via Web server logs, we monitor statistics such as:  
How many people visit our Web sites.  
Which pages people visit on our Web sites.  
From which domains our visitors come (e.g., "yahoo.com" or "google.com").  
Which browsers people use to visit our Web sites.  
While we gather this information, none of it is associated with you as an individual. We use these statistics to improve our Web sites, to monitor their performance, and to make it easier for you and other visitors to use.

### Log Files 

Like many other Web sites, www.filmyfolks.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Advertising/Cookies

We partner with third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. These companies may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information [not including your name, address, email address or telephone number] during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party advertising networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see

filmyfolks.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
We can be reached via e-mail at filmyfolks@gmail.com. If you have any questions or concerns, please feel free to email us at the same email address.

---
